ANDREW BOGGS

201 Seahawk Street, Las Vegas, NV 89145 | (H) 7025818914 | Drew702@icloud.com

Professional Summary

Responsible sales/ driver proficient in inventory and sales. Passionate and motivated, with a drive for excellence. 10 years in sales and vending experience. I have mastered the cold call sales but I feel I must move to higher ground. I'm great at adapting to any circumstance and a very fast learner I hold other passions in life as well as cooking and golf.

Skills

- Sales and Marketing
- Speaking
- English Language
- Critical Thinking
- Negotiation

- Customer and Personal Service
- Active Listening
- Service Orientation
- Reading Comprehension
- Administration and Management

Experience

Sales rep 02/2018 to Current

United Laboratories, Inc. – St. Charles, IL

Maintain and grow territory. Provide customer service along with solving billing issues. Keep track of inventory and order product accordingly. Call on cold calls as well as existing Accounts.

• Take quote requests or orders from dealers or customers.

Sales rep 04/2017 to 01/2018

American Builders – Las Vegas, NV

- Prepare proposals, quotes, contracts, or presentations for potential rain gutter clients
- Calculate potential rain gutter resources or arrange production for a particular site considering issues such as climate, shading, and roof orientation.

Driver sales rep 02/2013 to 01/2017

Bimbo Bakeries USA – Las Vegas, NV

 Collect money from customers, make change, and record transactions on customer receipts.

- Write customer orders and sales contracts according to company guidelines.
- Record sales or delivery information on daily sales or delivery record.
- Arrange merchandise and sales promotion displays or issue sales promotion materials to customers.

Education

High School Diploma: General

Jun 2000

Durango High School - Las Vegas, NV